AMOS GICHERO

WEB DEVELOPER

Phone: (404) 519-3561

Email:

amosgichero@gmail.com GitHub:

https://aithub.com/aichero

Linkein: https://

www.linkedin.com/in/amosgichero-579913a4/

Website:

www.amosgichero.com

Profile

I began my career as a software developer three years ago when I enrolled in college to study computer programming. Since graduating, I have enrolled in digitalCrafts an immersive coding bootcamp. I am passionate about technology and currently looking for opportunities in Atlanta. I have learned the following technologies in the past 3 years: Java, MySQL, Firebase, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript,

PostgreSQL, Python, Node, Express, jQuery, React native, React and

Redux.

Experience

Mobile App Hero

September 2017

Mobile app developer (internship) WeWork Tower Place, Atlanta

design and develop apps using Javascript frameworks, react and react native, node.

Web Development Projects (Bootcamp) Feb - June 2017

<u>vinylauction.com</u>: built using react, redux, node.js, express, stripe API, PostgreSQL

Smarta: built using node.js, express, handlebars,

Google and Yelp APIs, PostgreSQL

Shaw industries 2014-2017

Elutriation operator

Contributed to surpassing yearly records processing recycled carpet. I was consistently recognized for punctuality and working overtime.

Crete Carriers 2012-2014

Long haul truck driver

Accumulated over 150,000 miles without incidence delivering various goods nationally. Recognized as best rookie driver in 2013 for the Marietta, Georgia terminal.

Education

DigitalCrafts coding bootcamp

Feb - June 2017

Buckhead, Atlanta

Chattahoochee technical college

2014 - 2016

Marietta, Georgia

Associates degree computer programming

University of Canberra

2003 - 2006

Canberra, Australia

Bachelor business management and MIS